(knocking on door)
SHELDON:
Penny?
(knocks)
Penny.
(Penny:)You knocked more than usual.
(Sheldon:)Next time I might be in a rush,
(Sheldon:)it's good to have
a few in the bank.
(Penny:)Okay, what's up?
(Sheldon:)I'd like to discuss this party
(Sheldon:)that Amy and Bernadette
are throwing.
(Sheldon:)Since you and I are both
reluctant to go,
(Sheldon:)I think I've come up with a
perfect way for us to enjoy it.
(Penny:)Great, how?
(Sheldon:)We pretend we're aliens.
(Sheldon:)I'm not the best
at reading facial cues,
(Sheldon:)but I'm gonna say that you love
it and want to hear more.
(Leonard:)Now,
in the beloved novel
Hitchhiker's Guide
to the Galaxy,
(Sheldon:)an alien named Ford Prefect
pretended to be human
(Sheldon:)in order to blend in so that he
could write an entry about Earth
for The Hitchhiker's Guide
to the Galaxy,
(Sheldon:)which is a travel book
within the actual book,
(Sheldon:)which is also called
The Hitchhiker's Guide
to the Galaxy.
(Penny:)Okay, just one question.